<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zoom Out</string>
    <string name="infoVideo">Tap to experience informative universe travel</string>
    <string name="watchVideo">Tap to enjoy Earth zoom out</string>
    <string name="backward">Back</string>
    <string name="forward">Forw</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenu</string>
    <string name="mars">
        In 1976, Viking I photographed a mesa
        on Mars that had the appearance of a
        human face. Many individuals and
        organizations interested in
        extraterrestrial life argued that
        intelligent beings created the "Face."
        Though the Mars Global Surveyor
        (1997-2006) revealed that the "Face"
        was likely an optical illusion,
        believers in the "Face" charged NASA
        with stripping data from the new image
        before it was released to the public</string>
    <string name="jupiter">
        The Great Red Spot is the most noticeable
        feature on Jupiter\'s surface - a storm
        about 12,400 miles long and 7,500 miles
        wide, about two to three times larger than
        Earth. Winds at its oval edges can reach
        up to 425 mph (680 km/h). This giant storm
        was first recorded in 1831 but may have
        first been discovered in 1665.</string>
    <string name="saturn">
        It is made mostly of hydrogen and has
        a density which is less than water -
        which technically means that Saturn
        would float. The layers of hydrogen
        get denser further into the planet,
        eventually becoming metallic and
        leading to a hot interior core.</string>
    <string name="bisystem">
        Alpha Centauri is a special star -
        not only because it is the closest
        stellar system to the sun but also
        because it is one of the relatively
        few places in the Milky Way Galaxy
        that may offer terrestrial life
        conditions. If humanity looks for
        intelligent life elsewhere, then
        Alpha Centauri is an excellent candidate.</string>
    <string name="milky">
        Most larger galaxies have a supermassive
        black hole at the center, and the Milky
        Way is no exception. The center of our
        galaxy is called Sagittarius A*, a
        massive source of radio waves that is
        believed to be a black hole.</string>
    <string name="andromeda">
        For decades, astronomers have been
        saying that our home galaxy, the
        Milky Way, is destined someday to
        collide with the next-nearest spiral
        galaxy, in the direction of the
        constellation Andromeda. When they
        collide, our sun will likely be flung
        into a new region of galactic space.</string>
    <string name="gas">
        The trio of gas columns, located inside
        the Milky Way\'s Eagle Nebula, are
        factories for creating stars. The pillars
        themselves are the product of a massive
        nearby O-type star that sculpted the gas
        with its powerful winds. O-stars are the
        universe\'s largest, hottest stars and
        live short lives that wreak havoc on their
        environments.</string>
    <string name="quasars">
        Quasars are the brightest known
        objects in visible universe.
        According to scientists, a quasar
        is a compact region found at the
        central part of a massive galaxy
        and that this central region is
        actually surrounding supermassive
        black hole that sits at the very
        center of the galaxy. A supermassive
        black hole has mass equivalent to
        a billion solar masses.</string>
    <string name="we">
        The knowledge that the atoms that comprise
        life on earth - the atoms that make up the
        human body, are traceable to the crucibles
        that cooked light elements into heavy
        elements in their core under extreme temperatures
        and pressures. These stars- the high mass ones
        among them- went unstable in their later years-
        they collapsed and then exploded- scattering their
        enriched guts across the galaxy- guts made of all
        the fundamental ingredients of life itself. These
        ingredients become part of gas clouds that condense,
        collapse, form the next generation of solar systems-
        stars with orbiting planets. And those planets now
        have the ingredients for life itself. So that when
        I look up at the night sky, and I know that yes we
        are part of this universe, we are in this universe,
        but perhaps more important than both of those facts
        is that the universe is in us.(c)Neil deGrasse Tyson
    </string>
</resources>
